Joe Ulyatt

Software Engineer | Berlin, Germany

CONTACT

+44 7891 870 311

joewhocodes@gmail.com

@joewhocodes

github.com/joewhocodes

linkedin.com/in/joewhocodes

SKILLS

MERN Stack

React

Redux

JavaScript

Node.js

MongoDB

OOP

PHP

EDUCATION

Solent University

2010 - 2013

Music Production 2:1

SUMMARY

Creative Full Stack Developer with a passion for music and a knack for harmonising technology and creativity. Combining a solid technical foundation with a rich musical background, I bring a unique perspective to web development, enabling me to create engaging and intuitive digital experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer - 100Devs

Oct 2021 – Present

- Collaborating with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web applications using best practices
- Building semantically structured full stack web applications
- Applying agile methodologies like SCRUM for project management

Recent Projects:

No Strings Attached (Full Stack Web App) - MERN Stack Application that allows users to create profiles, search for and connect with other users in their area.

MovieGoJoe (React Web App) - React based application that allows users to check out the latest movie trailers, search and filter for movies they like and add them to a watchlist.

KingSR Hire (E-Commerce Web App) - E-Commerce Application that allows users to search for products, add them to a basket and request a quote from a selection of over 4000 rental items.

Other Projects: Pomodoro Joe, The Burrows Bed and Breakfast, NoStrings Seeder, CarJam, Coley Creates, Crazy Skins, JoeWhoCodes Portfolio

Full Stack Web Developer - JoeWhoCodes

Nov 2021 - Present

 Creating full stack web applications and static websites for different clients across small and medium size businesses. Also, consulted on SEO and social media strategy.

Technical Operations Manager - KSR | Bristol, UK

Feb 2017 to Nov 2021 - Bristol, UK

- Managing Current RMS software of over 4000 hire items
- Creation of rental arm of website pulling from the Current RMS Database
- Creating client quote templates using HTML, CSS and vanilla JS
- Lead AV Technician for live-streamed corporate conferences and live events